hi this video explains the importance of
Designing actionable error messages into
your apps so users can unblock
themselves and you can avoid getting
those support calls it's a clip from a
launch M video for 2023 relas Wave 2 but
it's equally relevant today let's turn
over to Sarah to tell us more about
it so as mentioned in the beginning one
of our main goals with the onboarding
framework has been to remove as much
friction as possible and avoid blocking
the way forward to users having a
successful start with business
Central but when getting hands on really
using a product people might run into
errors so in this release we have
improved our eror handling further and
introduced actionable errors providing
an easier way for users to unblock
themselves in context at the field level
such as refreshing the page or accepting
the recommended
actions and to learn more about
actionable errors and how you as a
partner can or developer can leverage
these new
patterns you should check out the
session about uh productivity features
in the
client um and as always you can find
more documentation on Microsoft learn to
learn more visit
aka.ms BC onboarding thank you for
watching
[Music]